[Music]
all of our products in one way or
another would be covering the treatment
or the loss of life due to kovat 19 if
we treat covet like 19 like any other
influence that type of virus it's
covered so give me an example
hospitalization related you would get
treatment benefits if you have other
complications it also would be covered
by the medical insurance if you're
covered by life insurance oftentimes
people our customers would have a life
insurance as well as a medical insurance
all bundled together that means that in
the in the case it goes to the extreme
where there's a loss of life be covered
by the life insurance as well as
described the whole life insurance
industry has waived the 30 30-day
waiting period for policies that were
written before the Chinese New Year
period and then also there's a grace
period for making payments for those
people who are affected by Kovach via
virus there's a 90 day grace period
right so we allow that at that time so
that it doesn't impact the effect of the
policy during that period when you're
affected by the virus we are also
announcing during this special period
that in addition to the policy benefits
if you're a policyholder
of Man Alive in the instance that you
are hospitalized for Kobe 19 we will be
offering 200 ringgit per day up to 30
days during the treatment period at the
hospital that are certified by the
Ministry of Health in addition in the
case of loss of life we will be
providing an additional ten thousand
ringgit an additional five thousand on
top of the ten thousand would be given
to those policyholders
that our medical staff that's the
special additional benefits that we will
give to our policyholders that are on
top of the the actual policy benefits so
during this period I think that
everybody should be more vigilant about
hygiene for those policyholders 90 life
and other other insurance company
policyholders in the general public you
know insurance companies will be there
for you when the claim situation happens
we will be very quick to ensure that we
can give me provide the guarantee letter
and that we will be there for all the
way through the treatment process so be
assured